AGNIESZKA KOŁOMYJEC

DATA ANALYST | JUNIOR DATA SCIENTIST

ABOUT ME

I am a Data Analyst with several years of professional experience in Controlling. Currently in the process of re-industry towards Python Developer and Data Scientist. I have half a year of design experience in SQL, Python and ML.

Currently, I focus my energy mainly on learning Python, ML, SQL and Power Bl...

I feel very comfortable in the space of numerical data and relations between them.

My future is related to programming and data analysis.

CONTACT

	+48 513-386-830
\boxtimes	agnieszkakolomyjec@gmail.com
in	https://www.linkedin.com/in/agniesz ka-kolomyjec/
	Tricity

SKILLS

SQL

Knowledge and practical skills allowing for independent performance of basic analyses. DQL DML DDL

PYTHON

Knowledge of libraries:

- Pandas
- NumPy
- Matplotlib
- Seaborn
- Scikit-learn

and basic knowledge of libraries:

- Black
- Pydantic

The tools I worked with:

- PostgreSQL
- Jupyter Notebook
- Git, GitHub
- PyCharm
- Visual Studio Code
- DBeaver
- Anaconda

EDUCATION

Infoshare Academy

01.2023-06.2023

BOOTCAMP DATA SCIENCE

The training included 240 hours of extramural workshops. It provided knowledge and practical skills in the field of: SQL, Python, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Git, Scrum, Tableau, Trello.

Infoshare Academy

01.2023-now

PYTHON ACADEMY. JUNIOR PYTHON DEVELOPER.

600 lessons with tasks and exercisesin Python.
On-line course preparing to obtain the PCEP-30-02 certificate

WSB University in Gdańsk

03.2014-03.2016

Title: Master

Finance and Accounting.
Accounting and controlling

UWM in Olsztyn

10.2010-09.2013

Bachelor Degree Enterprise Economics

WORK EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR DATA SCIENTIST

Infoshare Academy DatA Team

01.2023-06.2023

Ilmplementation of 4 group projects. Projects implemented in SQL, Python, ML and DL.

- 1. "How the level of happiness has changed in different countries over the years and what influenced the results? Based on the World Happiness Report from 2015-2019". Project implemented in SQL and Tableau. My task was to analyze issues in SQL. Project implemented in SCRUM.
- 2."Maybe fries with that." Analysis of restaurants for locations and menus in North America. The project was implemented in Python in JupyterNotebook, Visual Studio Code. Use of Pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib. My main task was to analyze health food restaurants.
- 3. "How expensive is health?" Objective of ML: determination of health costs based on the parameters of the insured. The purpose of the application: to help determine the health insurance threshold. The project was done data processing and analysis. Classifications or regressions were used. The test results are presented in the form of graphs and tables. The solution was supposed to bring an increase in business value. My task was to create two models (regression and random forest) with parameter tuning, counting metrics and visualization, as well as writing a summary and presenting the results, i.e. story telling. Master thesis in the scikit-learn library.
- 4. "Judge an album by its cover." Goal of DL: to distinguish music genres by their covers. Resnet network - convolutional block-based convolutional network and transfer learning VGG16 architecture with ImageNet scales. My task was to make a presentation and present it to the committee.

MACHINE LEARNING

Implementation of projects in Python, Machine Learning.

Practical application of:

- · models linear
- · logistic regression
- · decision tree
- · random forest
- xgboost
- PCA
- kmeans
- knn
- performing exploratory data analysis, data cleaning

DEEP LEARNING

Basic knowledge of:

- ANN
- CNN
- RNN

BI TOOLS

Basic knowledge of:

- Power BI and
- Tableau tools

allowing for the preparation of clear reports

MS EXCEL

Excel skills including:

- · advanced formulas
- functions
- · conditional filtering
- · manipulating/combining data
- pivot tables

ERP SYSTEM:

Asseco Softlab, SAP, Symfonia, Optima

ANALYTICS AND REPORTING

I have an analytical mind, thanks to which I draw the right conclusions and find answers to business questions.

Scrum and agile knowledge

LANGUAGES

- English B1/B2
- Russian A2

FINANCIAL ANALYST

NDI SA

 creating reports/models (Excel reports, Power BI), analysis of management needs, preparation of visualizations in cooperation with the accounting department

- analysis of deviations from assumptions in reports and project budgets
- design of the borrowing module for the system
- maternity leave 02.2022-02.2023

FINANCE SPECIALIST

02.2017-10.2017

10.2017-now

PrimaGran Sp. z o. o

- · support in the implementation of the ERP SAP system
- identification of processes taking place in the production company and translating them into procedures needed to implement the system
- preparation of reports for the needs of the Management Board (daily, monthly)

CONTROLLING SPECIALIST

07.2016-02.2017

KB Dom Sp. z o. o

- preparation of reports for the needs of the Management Board and the Supervisory Board, margin reporting
- preparation of investment project budgets
- control of deviations from budget assumptions, control of costs and cash flows
- analysis of contract conditions concluded with banks and subcontractors

FINANCIAL CONTROLLING SPECIALIST

Polnord SA

02.2014-06.2016

- financial supervision, financial management of two special purpose vehicles established for the implementation of residential investments, control of deviations from the assumptions budgetary control of costs, revenues and cf
- · reporting to the Management Board, Supervisory Board
- cooperation with the IT department managing the ERP and Work
 Flow system and close cooperation with the accounting department
- identifying the needs of the finance team in order to develop reporting tools

INDIVIDUAL CUSTOMER CARETAKER

Getin Noble Bank SA

08.2013-02.2014

· ongoing individual customer service.

I consent to the processing of personal data contained in this document for the implementation of recruitment processes conducted in accordance with with the Act of May 10, 2018 on the protection of personal data (Journal of Laws of 2018, item 1000) and in accordance with the Regulation of the European Parliamentand of the Council(EU) 2016/679 of 27 April 2016 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46 / EC(RODO).